23.03.2021 My resume



### Contacts

Phone: +48 503 011 256 E-mail: canderus111@gmail.com

### Tech skills

- HTML Basics
- CSS Basics
- Java Basics
- Profesional CNC programist
- · Mechanical Engineering
- Manufacturing Engineer

## Soft skills

- Teamwork
- · Self-organazing
- Problem Solving
- Open-minded

DOWNLOAD RESUME

# Tomasz Caputa

Manufacturing Engineer

I am Manufacturing engineer with 10 years of expierience as engineer and machine operator. I am passionate about new technologies and will to learn new skills. I see a future o engineering and technology in programming, machine learning and wide use of artificial intelligence. I see my future as a code developer.

# **Projects**

1. 6-dniowy Maraton Frontend od GoIT

# **Employment history**

Manufacturing Engineer in Collins Aerospace Wrocław

October 2016 - up to now

- CAD design
- CAM programming
- New projects implementation
- Process automation
- Cost reduction

#### CNC machine operator at Collins Aerospace Wrocław

January 2013 - October 2016

- CNC machine operator- Mazak system
- CNC machine operator- DMG Mori Celos system
- CNC machine operator- Fanuc system
- CNC machine operator- Studer system
- CMM measuring machines- Zeiss Celos system

#### CNC Machine operator at ANGA Bielsko-Biała

May 2011 - August 2012

• CNC Heidenhein Lathe

# Education

Mechanical Engineering, engineer degree Wrocław University of Science and Technology

September 2013 - June 2018

Mechatronic technician ZSEEiM Bielsko-Biała

October 2006 - June 2010